<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ParityDeals integrations. on</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/</link><description>Recent content in ParityDeals integrations. on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.priceon.app/integrations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Beehiiv</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/beehiiv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/beehiiv/</guid><description>Grow your Beehiiv newsletter subscriber base globally with Purchasing Power Parity (PPP) pricing. Seamlessly integrate Beehiiv newsletter and set up location-specific pricing and promotions. Create dynamic pricing now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Beehiiv with ParityDeals Connect Beehiiv with your existing Stripe account Go to your Beehiiv Setting Publication Premium and connect your Stripe account with your Beehiiv account.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Circle</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/circle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/circle/</guid><description>Get global customers by enabling Purchasing Power Parity (PPP) pricing for your Circle Community Running a community on on Circle? Easily link your circle community page and configure location-based pricing and promotions with just a few clicks. Attract users from all over the world! Create dynamic pricing now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Circle with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting ‘Create manually’ from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Framer</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/framer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/framer/</guid><description>Get global customers by enabling Purchasing Power Parity (PPP) pricing for your Framer sites Selling Framer templates or selling something on Framer? Easily link your Framer site and configure location-based pricing and promotions with just a few clicks. Attract customers from all over the world! Create dynamic pricing now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Framer with ParityDeals Connect ParityDeals with your existing platform ParityDeals integrate seamlessly with your preferred platform.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Kajabi course</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/kajabi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/kajabi/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Kajabi course Enable location based pricing in under 2 minutes with ParityDeals for your kajabi course Create dynamic pricing now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Kajabi with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting ‘Create manually’ from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown. Select deal types and setup product info Please note that you need to enter the exact website URL where you want to display the banner with the coupon code.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for LemonSqueezy</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/lemon-squeezy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/lemon-squeezy/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for LemonSqueezy Connect with your LemonSqueezy account and enable location based pricing and promotions for your products in under 2 minutes with ParityDeals. Connect Lemon Squeezy now -- 🎉 Exciting news! ParityDeals is now an official partner of Lemon Squeezy for dynamic pricing tool. Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Lemon Squeezy with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting Lemon Squeezy from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Podia</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/podia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/podia/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Podia Easily link your accounts and configure location-based pricing and promotions for your products with just a few clicks. Read how to integrate Podia Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Podia with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting ‘Create manually’ from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Substack</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/substack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/substack/</guid><description>Expand your Substack reach globally with Purchasing Power Parity (PPP) pricing Easily maximize your Substack newsletter subscription by adapting your pricing to local markets and leveraging purchasing power parity. Read how to integrate Substack How to integrate Substack with ParityDeals Create deals Go to ParityDeals and add your newsletter by selecting ‘Create manually’ from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity pricing for Chargebee</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/chargebee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/chargebee/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Chargebee Easily link your accounts and configure location-based pricing and promotions for your products with just a few clicks. Connect chargebee now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Chargebee with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting Chargebee from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown. Create and copy a Chargebee API key Navigate to settingsconfigureAPI and Webhooks in Chargebee, create a new API key (e.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity pricing for Dodo Payments</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/dodo-payments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/dodo-payments/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Dodo Payments Easily link your accounts and configure location-based pricing and promotions for your products with just a few clicks. Connect Dodo Payments now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Dodo Payments with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting Dodo Payments from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown.</description></item><item><title>Purchasing power parity pricing for Gumroad</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/gumroad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/integrations/gumroad/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity (PPP) pricing for Gumroad Connect with your Gumroad account and enable location based pricing and promotions for your products in under 2 minutes with ParityDeals. Connect Gumroad now Watch instruction video -- How to integrate Gumroad with ParityDeals Create deals Start adding your product by selecting Gumroad from the ‘Create deals’ dropdown.</description></item></channel></rss>