<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modern pricing and billing for the &lt;span>AI&lt;/span> era on</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/</link><description>Recent content in Modern pricing and billing for the &lt;span>AI&lt;/span> era on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>© 2023, Samay Labs, Inc . All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.paritydeals.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/homepage-v3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/homepage-v3/</guid><description>Modern pricing and billing for the AI era The all-in-one monetization engine that finds the right price for every customer. Power recurring billing, usage-based and outcome-driven models while leveraging data-driven pricing across billing, revenue recognition, retention and reporting—so you can focus on growing revenue. Book a demo Start free trial Metering Pricing plans Paywalls Targeting Experiments Trusted by the top companies.</description></item><item><title>ParityDeals guide</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/docs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Build nothing, Bill everything!</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/subscription-monetization-platform/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/subscription-monetization-platform/</guid><description>SUBSCRIPTION MONETIZATION PLATFORM Build nothing, Bill everything! Grow revenue with smart pricing, flexible paywalls, and a usage-based billing and metering solution. Focus on growth, not building billing infrastructure.
Join waitlist Trusted by the top modern companies -- Discover why leading creators and educators choose ParityDeals!</description></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/pricing/</guid><description>Pricing software which pays for itself 20x over Yearly(2 months free) Free $0 /mo 5k API hits/mo Get started 1 products 20 pricing banner Basic usage sales analytics Basic $41 /mo $49 /mo 50k API hits/mo Get started 5 products Unlimited pricing banner Auto-refreshing coupons Remove ParityDeals branding API Support VPN protection Tor Browser protection Proxy Server protection Standard most popular</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>ParityDeals, operated by Samay Labs, Inc. (“we,” “us,” or “our”), is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and safeguard your information when you use our services and website. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at hi@paritydeals.com.
1. Information We Collect # We collect the following types of information:
User Information: Basic details such as name and email address for authentication and account management purposes.</description></item><item><title>Stripe app</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/stripe-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/stripe-app/</guid><description>available on Stripe APP MARKETPLACE Pricing strategist for your global sales Capture 85% of the untapped market with location-based dynamic pricing directly via Stripe dashboard
Schedule a demo Get started for free Trusted by the top modern companies Discover why leading creators and educators choose ParityDeals!</description></item><item><title>Terms And Conditions</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description>1. Terms By accessing this Website, accessible from http://www.paritydeals.com/, you are agreeing to be bound by these Website Terms and Conditions of Use and agree that you are responsible for the agreement with any applicable local laws. If you disagree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from accessing this site. The materials contained in this Website are protected by copyright and trade mark law.
2. Use License Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials on ParityDeals Inc's Website for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only.</description></item><item><title>ParityDeals features.</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/features/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ParityDeals integrations.</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/integrations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/integrations/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ParityDeals Solutions.</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ParityDeals blog</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact us</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/contact/</guid><description>We've received your message. We will get back to you shortly. Oops! Something went wrong. Please email us at hi@paritydeals.com Please enter your Name and Email address. Name Email address Message Submit</description></item></channel></rss>