<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ParityDeals Solutions. on</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/</link><description>Recent content in ParityDeals Solutions. on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Info Products</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/info-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/info-products/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity pricing (PPP) for info products Maximize your sales by adapting your pricing to local markets and leveraging purchasing power parity. Book a demo Get started for free Increase your sales across the globe Overcome the challenges of reaching a global customer base. Your potential customers are around the world, but reaching and selling your software services to them is challenging due to differences in purchasing power across markets.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/newsletter/</guid><description>Expand your newsletter reach to the global market! Maximize your newsletter subscription by adapting your pricing to local markets and leveraging purchasing power parity. Book a demo Get started for free Increase your subscription count across the globe Overcome the challenges of reaching a global user base. Your potential readers are around the world, but reaching and selling your newsletter subscription to them is challenging due to differences in purchasing power across markets.</description></item><item><title>Online Courses</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/online-courses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/online-courses/</guid><description>Expand the reach of your online courses to the global market! Maximize your online course sales by adapting your pricing to local markets and leveraging purchasing power parity. Book a demo Get started for free Increase your sales across the globe Overcome the challenges of reaching a global student base. Your potential students are around the world, but reaching and selling your course to them is challenging due to differences in purchasing power across markets.</description></item><item><title>SaaS Business</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/saas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/solution/saas/</guid><description>Unlock global opportunities for your SaaS business Maximize your sales by adapting your pricing to local markets and leveraging purchasing power parity. Book a demo Get started for free Increase your sales across the globe Overcome the challenges of reaching a global customer base. Your potential customers are around the world, but reaching and selling your software services to them is challenging due to differences in purchasing power across markets.</description></item></channel></rss>