<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ParityDeals blog on</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in ParityDeals blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 09:19:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Geographical pricing: The growth strategy your competitors don’t want you to know about.</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/geographical-pricing-the-growth-strategy-your-competitors-dont-want-you-to-know-about./</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/geographical-pricing-the-growth-strategy-your-competitors-dont-want-you-to-know-about./</guid><description>Are you struggling to increase your sales and revenue despite investing time and resources in different growth channels and ads? Well, have you considered implementing geographical pricing for your SaaS product? By setting prices that match the local market, you can increase your sales by 20-70% on average, outsmart your competition, and even expand globally.
Every country and region has its own unique cost of living, level of demand, willingness to pay, and market competition.</description></item><item><title>From pricing chaos to growth: Mastering price experimentation for your SaaS company.</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/from-pricing-chaos-to-growth-mastering-price-experimentation-for-your-saas-company./</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/from-pricing-chaos-to-growth-mastering-price-experimentation-for-your-saas-company./</guid><description>As a SaaS company, one of the most important levers for growth is your pricing strategy. But how do you determine the best pricing for your SaaS offering? The answer is through ongoing price experimentation.
Price experimentation means frequently making incremental changes to your pricing and offers to see how your customers and revenue respond. By testing different price points, bundles, discounts, and models, you can gain valuable data and insights to optimize your pricing.</description></item><item><title>Increase your sales with localized pricing and promotions as knowledge entrepreneurs and creators.</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/increase-your-sales-with-localized-pricing-and-promotions-as-knowledge-entrepreneurs-and-creators./</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/increase-your-sales-with-localized-pricing-and-promotions-as-knowledge-entrepreneurs-and-creators./</guid><description>The digital era has brought numerous opportunities for knowledge content creators to reach a global audience. However, one of the most significant challenges faced by these creators is pricing their products and services to accommodate the differences in purchasing power across countries. By offering localized pricing and country-specific deals, creators can increase their sales without investing too much time and money. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how big companies are capitalizing on localization and how ParityDeals can make this process more accessible and cost-effective for knowledge content creators.</description></item><item><title>How I increased revenue by offering purchasing power parity pricing</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/how-i-increased-revenue-by-offering-purchasing-power-parity-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/how-i-increased-revenue-by-offering-purchasing-power-parity-pricing/</guid><description>Last year I quit my full-time job to focus entirely on my side projects. My most selling product is an open-sourced JavaScript library called lightGallery.
I was getting visitors to my website from all over the world. But sales mainly were happening from the United States, Canada, and a few parts of Europe.
Because the pricing was US-centric and people from other parts of the globe could not afford it.So I decided to offer purchasing power parity pricing.</description></item><item><title>Geographical Pricing: Outshine competitors in every market</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/geographical-pricing-outshine-competitors-in-every-market/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/geographical-pricing-outshine-competitors-in-every-market/</guid><description>Hey there! Have you ever wondered how some companies seem to nail their pricing strategy in different parts of the world?
Well, buckle up because we&amp;rsquo;re about to dive into the exciting world of geographical pricing – the secret sauce that could take your business to new heights!
In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll break down geographical pricing in a super friendly way, share some awesome examples, and give you the lowdown on how to implement it effectively.</description></item><item><title>Kajabi Pricing: Discover your ideal business plan</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/kajabi-pricing-discover-your-ideal-business-plan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/kajabi-pricing-discover-your-ideal-business-plan/</guid><description>As a creator, after extensive research and exploration, I have come to realize that choosing the right platform for your business can be quite a task, especially with so many options out there but if you’re considering Kajabi, you’re on the right track. Kajabi is a powerful all-in-one platform designed to help entrepreneurs and small businesses create, market, and sell online courses, membership sites, and other digital products.
Table of Contents # What is Kajabi?</description></item><item><title>Why purchasing power parity pricing is a must for digital products?</title><link>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/why-purchasing-power-parity-pricing-is-a-must-for-digital-products/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.paritydeals.com/blog/why-purchasing-power-parity-pricing-is-a-must-for-digital-products/</guid><description>Purchasing power parity is an economic term for measuring prices at different locations.
It helps you determine how much your product should cost in each country.
For example, At 6.98 U.S. dollars, Switzerland has the most expensive Big Mac hamburger sold by McDonald&amp;rsquo;s. Concurrently the cost of a Big Mac was $5.81 in the U.S. and $2.55 in India.
Why Is Purchasing Power Parity Important? # Parity pricing is a proven, common-sense way that has been used by businesses for years.</description></item></channel></rss>