<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Create Deals on</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/</link><description>Recent content in Create Deals on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Location based deals</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/location-based-deals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/location-based-deals/</guid><description>Getting Started: # There are two ways to set up location-based discounts for your products. You can either add discounts via Integrated platforms or add them manually.
Set up discount via Integrated platforms # If you are selling your prodcut via Gumroad,Stripe,Paddle,Whop,Lemon Squeezy and Chargebee this is the best option to set up discount coupons for your products.
This way, you can connect with your existing platforms, choose existing products, review the discount rules and automatically create discount coupons.</description></item><item><title>Holidays based deals</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/holiday-deals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/holiday-deals/</guid><description>Getting Started: # There are two ways to set up holiday-based discounts for your products. You can either add discounts via Integrated platforms or add them manually.
Set up discount via Integrated platforms # If you are selling your prodcut via Gumroad, Stripe, Paddle, Whop, Lemon Squeezy and Chargebee this is the best option to set up discount coupons for your products.
This way, you can connect with your existing platforms, choose existing products, review the discount rules and automatically create discount coupons.</description></item><item><title>Time based deals</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/time-based-deals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/docs/create-deals/time-based-deals/</guid><description>Getting Started: # At the moment, creating time-based deals is supported only for Integrated platforms with ParityDeals.
Select product. # Click on the Create Deals tab from the left-hand side main navigation. Select the platform you want to integrate ParityDeals with from the dropdown list , Currently ParityDeals has integration with Gumroad, Stripe, Paddle, Whop, Lemon Squeezy and Chargebee. you will be required to connect with the integrated platform for the first time.</description></item></channel></rss>