<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ParityDeals features. on</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/features/</link><description>Recent content in ParityDeals features. on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.priceon.app/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create time-based flash deals to attract more users in limited time</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/features/time-based-discounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/features/time-based-discounts/</guid><description>Create time-based flash deals to attract more users in limited time Run multiple days discount sales or run for a time duration. Run dynamic sales deals by choosing discount drop percentage. Get started for free Get started for free How it works? Select your products Add product from your Gumroad account or from your website Select discount duration Select discount start time, drop percentage, discount duration Customize discount banner Personalized your discount banner as per your website theme Measure sales performance Make sales strategy by measuring your sales performance by location Key features Setup discount start time, drop percentage, discount duration Run time-based dynamic discounts by selecting discount start time, drop percentage, or duration range.</description></item><item><title>Optimize pricing across countries based on Purchasing Power Parity</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/features/purchasing-power-parity-discounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/features/purchasing-power-parity-discounts/</guid><description>Optimize pricing across countries based on Purchasing Power Parity. Purchasing power of each country is different. Setup various discount rules for different countries to maximize revenue. Get started for free Get started for free How it works? Select your products Add product from your Gumroad account or from your website Select discount rules Select rules for countries based on the Purchasing Power Parity Customize discount banner Personalized your discount banner as per your website theme Measure sales performance Make sales strategy by measuring your sales performance by location Key features Pre-defined discount rules Set up your discount banner with a few clicks by using our predefined discount rules which you can use with a single click.</description></item><item><title>Run festivals and holidays discount deals to boost your sales</title><link>https://www.priceon.app/features/holiday-based-discounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.priceon.app/features/holiday-based-discounts/</guid><description>Run festivals and holidays discount deals to boost your sales Provide discount by festival, holidays, product launch, success milestones, or on your Birthday :) Get started for free Get started for free How it works? Select your products Add product from your Gumroad account or from your website Manage holidays discount Create discount codes for different holidays or on your Birthday :) Customize discount banner Personalized your discount banner as per your website theme Measure sales performance Make sales strategy by measuring your sales performance by location Key features Pre-selected holidays list Set up your holidays deals banner with our pre-selected holidays list from various countries.</description></item></channel></rss>